<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollingView</string>
    <string name="description">Every 60 seconds, 146 cubic yards of sandcastles are being built worldwide. The “smoke-line” left by an airplane is really water vapor. A longer lasting, wider line could be the tell-tale sign of an impending storm while a short lasting one indicates low-humidity air and fair weather. Despite the movies, it’s impossible to open the plane’s door mid-flight. The cabin is so pressurized that it would take several strong people to push it open since it must be moved in and turned slightly before opening. During an average lift off, a commercial jet takes off at 550-580 miles per hour. The tallest mountain in the world, Mauna Kea, is located in Hawaii. It’s about twice the base to peak height of Mount Everest and when measured from the seafloor is over 32,000 feet high. The word Pennsylvania is misspelled “Pensylvania” on the Liberty Bell, which tourists can now see in Philadelphia. The city of Chicago is where the first ever ferris wheel was invented in the 1893 World’s Fair. Battle Creek, Michigan makes more cereal than any other city in the world. Montana has three times as many cows than it does people.For our Walking Dead fans out there, which has scenes filmed in Atlanta, the old name of the city in Georgia was Terminus. Sound familiar?
According to statistics gathered in 2014, the U.S. has over 19,000 landing facilities and 378 airports.
The Great Smoky Mountain National Park is actually the most visited national park in the United States!  They had more than 11.3 million recreational visitors in 2017.
Noah’s Ark Waterpark in Wisconsin is the largest outdoor water park in America. It has over 70 acres of water slides! The Dells is also home to the nation’s largest indoor water park resort, Kalahari Resort (125,000 square feet).
Fear not! Although Michigan is known as the “Wolverine State,” there are no longer any wolverines in the state. One was spotted in 2004, however, that was the first found in over 200 years.
The Finger Lakes area in New York is the largest wine producing region in the United States, besides California.
The famous Ben and Jerry’s Ice Cream Company gives their ice cream waste to local Vermont farmers. The hogs love to devour all flavors…well, except Mint Oreo, which they are picky about.Maine is the only state in the US with a  name that is only one syllable.
Ninety percent of the country’s toothpick supply is made in Maine. They’re also famous for harvesting the most lobsters and producing the most broccoli.
There is a house in Rockport that is made entirely out of newspapers.
Both volleyball and basketball were invented in Massachusetts. It is also where the first sewing machine and computer were invented.
Atlantic City, New Jersey is home to the longest boardwalk in the world.
Virginia is the only state that has the same state tree and state flower, the Flowering Dogwood Tree.
The Outer Banks of North Carolina is the 3rd largest destination for weddings in the US, third only to Hawaii and Las Vegas. It’s estimated that there are more than 3,500 weddings hosted in the Outer Banks every year!
The population of Myrtle Beach, South Carolina jumps from 30,000 to over 350,000 in the summer months.
Parts of Forest Gump were filmed in Savannah, Georgia…most notably the bench Forest sat on the north side of Chippewa Square, for the famous “Life is like a box of chocolates” quote. The bench is now located in the Savannah History Museum.
When you’re in the middle of the Panhandle of Florida, be careful about the settings on your phone. Some travelers will set their clocks to manual so it doesn’t keep switching between Eastern and Central time zones.
The soil in Baldwin County, Alabama around the Gulf Shores area became so fertile after the 1906 hurricane that vegetables grew to huge proportions. Sweet Potatoes were the size of water buckets and cabbages weighed up to 20 pounds a piece!
In Galveston, Texas, it is illegal to have a camel run loose on the beach.
Gatorade was named after the University of Florida Gators where the drink was developed on the east coast of Florida.
The temperature in Naples has never reached 100 degrees, the record is 99 set in Sept. of 1986
Idaho has the most rivers! With 3,100 miles of water, it’s the most out of all the states.
The name Tahoe in California comes from a mispronunciation of the Washoe Native American name for Lake Tahoe, da ow a ga, translating, “edge of the lake.”
Cutting down an endangered cactus in Phoenix, Arizona could land you one year in prison! It can take up to 100 years for a Saguaro cactus to grow, so it’s no wonder why!
The best preserved meteor crater in the world is in Winslow, Arizona.
Viva Las Vegas! Bugsy Siegel named his casino the Flamingo after the long legs of his showgirl girlfriend.
60,000 pounds of shrimp are consumed in Las Vegas every day, almost as much as in the whole United States.
The Ancient Mayans of Cancun cultivated tree sap to make chewing gum.</string>
</resources>